datingskillsreview.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy

PUL is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy is provided for you to understand how we use your personal information (aka personally identifiable information). By accessing the PUL site, you take responsibility for reading and understanding this information. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, in part or whole, and do not wish to be bound by it, please discontinue accessing / utilizing our website. 

This privacy policy describes what information PUL collects, how we collect it, and our information sharing practices, including: 

  1. [Information We Collect from Our Users and How We Collect It](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#1)
  2. [How We Use Personally Identifiable Information](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#2)
  3. [Cookies / Clear GIFs and How We Use Them](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#3)
  4. [How We Store Your Information](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#4)
  5. [Personal Information of Minors](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#5)
  6. [Links to Other Sites](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#6)
  7. [Disclaimer](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/privacy/#7)

## Information We Collect from Our Users and How We Collect It

PUL collects personally identifying information from our users during online registration. Generally, this personally identifiable information includes the user’s name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free newsletters and/or access to our website content. Each individual user provides this information to PUL. We do not contact individuals unless specifically requested by that individual, or in the event that they have signed up to receive our free newsletters. 

Upon providing PUL with personally identifiable information in connection with utilizing our website, you willingly consent to our communicating with you regarding our website services using that information. 

Though PUL strives to take the appropriate measures to protect your personally identifiable information against unauthorized or unlawful use, be advised that we cannot 100% guarantee the security of data transmitted over the Internet. Therefore, transmitting personally identifiable information over the Internet is ultimately at the sender’s / user’s own risk. 

## How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

The personally identifiable information you provide is used for internal marketing purposes only. PUL does not sell, exchange, or release personally identifiable information (e.g., name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit data, etc.). Your information is not shared with any other third party or company. 

However, PUL may use third-party website analytics tools such as Google to collect visitor traffic information on our site (e.g., search terms used within the site, IP address, browser type, page views, site navigation patterns) 

## Cookies / Clear GIFs and How We Use Them

The PUL site utilizes "cookies" and clear GIFs to collect information about how our site is used. If your web browser permits, a cookie is a small data text file that a website stores on your computer's hard drive that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies help a website recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and saves (remembers) any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the personally identifiable information from your computer. 

To help us measure advertising effectiveness, PUL occasionally works with third-party service partners that utilize clear GIFs (a.k.a. pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons, or action tags). Similar in function to cookies, clear GIFs are tiny graphics (smaller than cookies and invisible on the page) with a unique identifier used to track visitor traffic and behavior to and on our site . Clear GIFs are not tied to your personally identifiable information. 

Clear GIFs often work in conjunction with existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website. For example, if a user visited "www.Acompany.com", which uses a company's clear GIF, the website matches the clear GIFs identifier and the company's cookie ID number, to show the previous online behavior for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the company. We sometimes provide such information to our third-party advertising service partners. However, that information can only be utilized by our partner for our benefit and never includes personally identifiable information. 

## How We Store Your Information

Your information is stored locally on our own website database or on the list server that delivers a PUL newsletter. Only authorized individuals who help manage our internal databases and those lists in order to deliver e-mail to PUL newsletter subscribed members can access your information. 

All PUL newsletters include an unsubscribe link. You can unsubscribe yourself from our newsletters at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link. To change your information, contact us at var email = "support"; var domain = "datingskillsreview.com"; document.write("["+email+"@"+domain+"](https://www.datingskillsreview.com/%22%22+%22mail%22+%22to:%22+email+%22@%22+domain+%22/%22)"). 

## Personal Information of Minors

The PUL website, its use, and content are intended for adults only. Minors (under 18 years of age) are advised to refrain from using our site, providing any personally identifiable information online, and submitting / posting any content on our website. PUL does not knowingly accept, use, or circulate any personally identifiable information from or about minors. 

## Links to Other Sites

The PUL website contains links that redirect to third-party websites (e.g., for product purchasing and marketing purposes) whose privacy policies and practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for third-party website privacy policies and have no control over the information and content that is used, submitted to, collected, or advertised by them. Please refer the privacy policy of these other websites. Our privacy policy does not apply to these third-party sites and PUL has no control over the personally identifiable information they may collect, process, store, or use. Please refer to the privacy policy of those websites. 

## Disclaimer

PUL reserves the right and discretion to modify this privacy policy, in part or in whole, at any time. Any privacy policy updates we will posted to this website page. This policy was revised January 17, 2014. Please direct any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy to [support@datingskillsreview.com](mailto:support@datingskillsreview.com) . You may also contact: 

PUL  
Unit 1010, 10/F, Miramar Tower, 132 Nathan Road,  
Tsim Sha Tsui, Kowloon,  
Hong Kong
